Guide to the Duplex Advertising Company. Billboard Images and Records, 1964-1993 and undated RL.00339
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duplex Advertising Company. Billboard Images and records
circa 1964-1993 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duplex Advertising Company
RL.00339
7.5 Linear Feet
5300 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. There may be a 48-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Duplex Advertising Company. Billboard Images and Records, 1964-1993 and undated, were donated by Bill James, of the Duplex Advertising Company, in 1998.
Historical Note
Chronology
1925 Duplex Advertising founded by R. V. Miller, Sr. with two partners in Austin, Tex.
1925-1980s Duplex Advertising-owned billboards stretched across the central Texas area, from San Marcos to Temple. Involved with the manufacture and installation of electric on-premise signage
1960s The Duplex Advertising Company of Temple, in Temple, Tex., created
1970s The Duplex Electric Signs company created as a separate entity
1980 The portion of the business around Austin was sold to the Rollins Outdoor Advertising Company. The Duplex Electric Sign Company was sold to Bajon Signs (Austin, Tex.)
1981 R. V. Miller, Jr. bought Duplex Advertising Company of Temple from his father and brother (Will). R. V. Miller, Sr. and Will Miller managed the Duplex Land Company and other family interests
1980s-1990s Duplex added building new structures and acquiring several companies, including Strasburger Enterprises of Temple, and the eastern inventory of Norwood Outdoor Advertising (covering Killeen, Copperas Cove, Gatesville, and Bosque counties)
1990 Will Miller died
1993 R. V. Miller, Jr. died
1994 Duplex Advertising was operated in trust for Miller's heirs, with R. Keith Johnson as president, and Tom Wicker and Dale Schigut as vice-presidents
1998 Duplex Advertising was sold to Advantage Outdoor. Lamar Outdoor Advertising has since acquired Advantage's holdings
Biographical Note
R. V. (Bob) Miller, Jr. was born in Austin, Tex. in 1932. He served in the US Navy as a photographer's mate and then attended Texas Techonlogical University where he received a BBA in Advertising and an MBA. He began his career in outdoor advertising at San-Tex Advertising, in San Angelo, Tex. From there, Miller founded and worked with the Duplex Advertising Company in Austin, Duplex Electric Signs, and Duplex Advertising Company in Temple, Tex. He also taught courses in economics, advertising, marketing, and statistics. One of his articles included in the collection addresses the application of advertising realities in the classroom.
Collection Overview
The Duplex Advertising Company. Billboard Images and Records spans the period 1964-1993 and documents the outdoor advertising work of this company in the central Texas area, primarily through photographs, negatives and slides of billboards. Many of the images are in color. A large number of the images are of national campaigns advertised in central Texas, as well as billboards, signs and posters of local Texas business services. In addition, a handful of articles written by R. V. Miller, Jr. for a number of publications, as well as other printed material and miscellaneous items from the Duplex Advertising Company, are present. Some of these articles, along with the images themselves, provide examples of commercial art and design in the outdoor advertising arena. The collection includes outdoor advertising images from national clients such as Kentucky Fried Chicken, Chevrolet, Coca Cola, Coors, Wendy's, Hardee's, and Taco Bell, and Texas clients such as Lone Star and Pearl beers.
Related materials may be found in other outdoor advertising collections, including the Outdoor Advertising Association of America Archives, the Garrett Orr Papers, the Howard Scott Papers, the John Paver Papers, the John E. Browning Papers, the R.C. Maxwell Co. Records, and the Strobridge Collection.
Slides (photographs); Temple (Tex.) -- History; Billboards; Advertising, Outdoor -- United States; Advertising -- Brand name products; Advertising agencies -- Texas; Advertising, Outdoor -- United States -- Texas; Photographs; Advertising -- Posters; Advertising agencies; Advertising agencies -- United States; Billboards -- United States; Advertising -- History; Advertising, Outdoor -- History; Advertising, Outdoor -- Posters; Signs and signboards; Negatives (photographic); Posters -- Design; Poster, American -- 20th century -- United States; Commercial art -- United States; Duplex Advertising Company; General Motors Corporation. Chevrolet Motor Division; Hardee's Food Systems; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; Duplex Advertising Company; Adolph Coors Company; Coca-Cola Company; Wendy's International; Taco Bell (Firm); Pearl Brewing Company; Miller, R.V., Jr; Miller, R. (Bob) V.; Lone Star Brewing Company; Kentucky Fried Chicken (Firm)
- Printed Material and Miscellaneous Items Series, 1969-1991 and undated
  Scope and Contents note
  Contains printed materials and articles about outdoor advertisng, written primarily by R. V. Miller, Jr. There are also some miscellaneous items, such as a permit tag that would have been attached to a billboard, and company stationery. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Company miscellaneous items (Box 1)
    - Billboard permit tag, Tex., 1977 (Box 1)
    - Poster placement sheet for Richland Cigarettes, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Printed material
    - Applying Advertising Realities in the Classroom, in Southwest Advertising & Marketing, 1976 Nov. (Box 1)
    - Billboards: The Outdoor Advertising Medium, 1984 (Box 1)
    - Billboard Rotary: The Outdoor Advertising Medium, 1991 (Box 1)
    - OBIE Awards booklet, IOA (includes OBIE winner from Duplex), 1986 (Box 1)
    - Outdoor Advertising in the Year 5000 Plus-A Current Report, in Southwest Advertising & Marketing, 1978, Oct. (Box 1)
    - Prudence Puresmart in Media! A Melodramatic Moment, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Reach and Re-reach, undated (Box 1)
    - Selling the Seasonal Business, in Signs of the Times, 1980 Oct. (Box 1)
    - The Delightful Decline of San Angelo, Texas: A Report of Interest to Interested People by Outdoor Advertising, by San-Tex Advertising, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Stationery
    - Thank You and Welcome Home cards, envelope (Box 1)
- Photographs By Product Series, 1964-1985 and undated
  Photographs are organized into two groups: those of billboards produced by Duplex, and billboards produced by other outdoor advertising companies. Photographs of competitor's billboards mainly date from the 1980s. Each group is arranged alphabetically by product type.
  - Group 1: Billboards produced by Duplex
    - Airlines, 1971 Nov. (Box 2)
    - Amusement/ Sports, 1981 Aug.-1982 Jan., 6 sheets (Box 2)
    - Appliances/ Electronics, 1968 May-1981 Aug., 4 sheets (Box 2)
    - Automobiles and Trucks, 1981 Oct., 7 sheets (Box 2)
      [See also Box 4]
    - Banks, 1965 Feb.-1985 Apr., 27 sheets (Box 2)
    - Beer, 1966 Jan., 12 sheets (Box 2)
    - Boats, undated, 2 sheets (Box 2)
    - Cigarettes, 1982 Jan., 4 sheets (Box 2)
    - Clothing, 1971 Jan., 2 sheets (Box 2)
    - Clubs, 1982 Jan., 2 sheets (Box 2)
    - Coke, undated, 2 sheets (Box 2)
    - Creek Place, undated, 4 sheets (Box 2)
    - Duplex, undated (Box 2)
    - Events, undated, 4 sheets (Box 2)
    - Food and Grocery Stores, 1984 Aug., 7 sheets (Box 2)
    - Funeral Homes, undated, 3 sheets (Box 2)
    - Furniture/ Home furnishings, 1972 Mar.-1980 Aug., 7 sheets (Box 2)
    - Gasoline, 1971 Nov. (Box 3)
    - Hardware, undated, 2 sheets (Box 3)
    - Jewelry, 1980 Aug.-1981 Oct., 3 sheets (Box 3)
    - Locations, 1964 Aug.-1982 Jan., 19 sheets (Box 3)
    - Malls, 1981 Oct.-1985 Apr., 2 sheets (Box 3)
    - Marlboro, undated, 4 sheets (Box 3)
    - Medical, undated, 2 sheets (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1981 Aug., 10 sheets (Box 3)
    - Motels, 1971 Jan.-1981 July, 10 sheets (Box 3)
    - Political, undated, 5 sheets (Box 3)
    - Public Service, 1982 Jan., 6 sheets (Box 3)
    - Radio, undated, 5 sheets (Box 3)
    - Raid, undated (Box 3)
    - Real Estate, 1981 July 1981-1982 Jan., 16 sheets (Box 3)
    - Restaurants, 1970 June-1982 Apr., 28 sheets (Box 3)
    - Retail Stores, 1976 Dec.-1981 Oct., 4 sheets (Box 3)
    - Seed Companies, undated, 2 sheets (Box 3)
    - Southland (7-11), undated, 3 sheets (Box 3)
    - Storm Damage, undated, 4 sheets (Box 4)
    - Suzuki, 1982 Jan., 2 sheets (Box 4)
    - Telephone, undated, 2 sheets (Box 4)
    - TV Stations, undated, 4 sheets (Box 4)
      [See below]
  - Group 2: Billboards produced by competing companies
    - Apartments and Rentals, undated, 4 sheets (Box 4)
    - Automobiles, undated, 3 sheets (Box 4)
    - Banks, circa 1985, 3 sheets (Box 4)
    - Billboard Companies, circa 1985 (Box 4)
    - Cigarettes, circa 1985, 3 sheets (Box 4)
    - Clothing, circa 1985, 3 sheets (Box 4)
    - Computers and Videos, undated, 2 sheets (Box 4)
    - Entertainment, circa 1985, 2 sheets (Box 4)
    - Express Mail Service, circa 1985 (Box 4)
    - Flowers, circa 1985, 2 sheets (Box 4)
    - Food, circa 1985, 4 sheets (Box 4)
    - Funeral Homes, circa 1985 (Box 4)
    - Health, Hospitals, Doctors, Fitness Clubs, undated, 5 sheets (Box 4)
    - Home Improvement, circa 1985, 3 sheets (Box 4)
    - Jewelry, circa 1985 (Box 4)
    - Liquor, circa 1985, 6 sheets (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1985, 10 sheets (Box 4)
    - Public Service, undated, 7 sheets (Box 4)
    - Radio/ TV, undated, 6 sheets (Box 4)
    - Restaurants, circa 1985, 9 sheets (Box 4)
- Photographs By Client Series, 1964-1993 and undated
  Arranged alphabetically. Selected client names with large numbers of photographs are listed under the letter group (i.e. A, B, C, etc.) with their own entry. Additional clients for whom there are a significant but not large number of photographs are collected in folders marked Various at the end of each letter run.
  - A, 1982 Jan., 17 sheets (Box 5)
    - Alcoa, undated (Box 5)
    - American Bank, undated (Box 5)
    - Aquarena Springs, undated (Box 5)
    - Arby's, 1982 Jan. (Box 5)
    - A-various including: Active Citizens for Temple, Altrusa Club of Temple, Archie's Hamburger Place, Arts and Crafts Show, undated (Box 5)
  - B, 1980 Aug.-1991 Dec., 62 sheets
    - Best Western, undated (Box 5)
    - Big Red (beverage), 1983 May (Box 5)
    - Budweiser 1985 July (Box 5)
    - Burger King, undated (Box 5)
    - B-various including: Bell County Youth Fair and Livestock Show, Benchmark Inn, Bobby's Burgers and Ice Cream, Buds Western Store, undated (Box 5)
  - C, 1966 May-1985 Apr., 70 sheets
    - Cablevision, undated (Box 5)
    - Citizens National Bank, undated (Box 5)
    - Coca Cola, undated (Box 5)
    - Comfort Inn, undated (Box 5)
    - Coors, 1981 Apr. (Box 5)
    - C-various including: CAC, Casa Ole, Cen-Tex Young Farmers, undated (Box 5)
  - D, 1981 Oct., 52 sheets (Box 6)
    - Dairy Queen, undated (Box 6)
    - Doc's 1 Stop, undated (Box 6)
    - Dr. Pepper, undated (Box 6)
    - Duplex, undated (Box 6)
    - D-various including: Dell Computers, DeWitt Jewelers, Doyle Phillips Steak House, Doyle's Auto Supply and Machine Shop, undated (Box 6)
  - E/F, 1980 Aug.-1982 Apr., 64 sheets
    - Exxon, undated (Box 6)
    - First Med, undated (Box 6)
    - First National Banks of Temple, undated (Box 6)
    - Ford, 1980 Aug. 12 (Box 6)
    - E/F-various including: Elaine's Bridal Shop and Prom Gowns, Festival of Flags, First Baptist of Belton, First National Bank of Georgetown, Fountain of Beauty Inc, undated (Box 6)
  - G, 1982 Jan., 35 sheets
    - Garlyn Shelton Autoplex, undated (Box 6)
    - Grandy's, undated (Box 6)
    - GreenGo's Liquor, undated (Box 6)
    - G-various including: Giovanni's Restaurant, Girl Scouts, Gold's Department Store, Guaranty Federal Savings Bank, undated (Box 6)
  - H, 1966 Nov.-1993, 19 sheets (Box 7)
    - Hardee's, undated (Box 7)
    - Harper-Talasek Funeral Homes, undated (Box 7)
    - H-various including: Heart O'Texas Fair and Rodeo, Holland Corn Festival, Holland Hornets, Hostages public service, undated (Box 7)
  - I/J, 1965 Aug.-1981 Oct., 32 sheets
    - Interfirst, undated (Box 7)
    - Jim's Dive Shop, undated (Box 7)
    - Johnson Brothers Ford Dealership, undated (Box 7)
    - I/J-various including: Inner Space Cavern, Jackie's Fashions, Jackson Marine, undated (Box 7)
  - K, 62 sheets
    - K-Bob's, undated (Box 7)
    - Kentucky Fried Chicken, undated (Box 7)
    - Kings Daughters Hospital and Clinic, undated (Box 7)
    - King's Fried Chicken, undated (Box 7)
    - K-various including: Ka-Tee Shoes, KCEN-TV, Knights of Columbus, KXXV-25, undated (Box 7)
  - L, 1981 Nov.-1986 Sept., 45 sheets
    - La Quinta Inn, undated (Box 7)
    - Lone Star Beer, undated (Box 7)
    - Longhorn Cavern State Park, 1981 Nov. (Box 7)
    - L-various including: Lastovica Jewelers, Law Insurance Pirates, Leprechauns Landing Day Care Center, The Lion in Aladdin's Lamp, Live Oak Park, undated (Box 7)
  - M, 1991 Dec. and undated, 46 sheets (Box 8)
    - Marlboro, undated (Box 8)
    - McDonald's, 1991 Dec. (Box 8)
    - Mobil, undated (Box 8)
    - Monarch Homes, undated (Box 8)
    - M-various including: Market Place Shopping Center, Midget Café, Milo Computer Services, Mr. Gatti's, Mrs. Robinson's Neighborhood, undated (Box 8)
  - N/O, 1981 Nov.-1991 Dec., 16 sheets
    - Norrell Temporary Services, undated (Box 8)
    - Oak Creek Homes, 1991 Dec. (Box 8)
    - Outdoor America, undated (Box 8)
    - N/O-various including: Nash Phillips/Copus, Natural Bridge Caverns, Oatmeal Festival, undated (Box 8)
  - P, 32 sheets
    - People's National Bank, undated (Box 8)
    - Pepsi, undated (Box 8)
    - Piccadilly Cafeteria, undated (Box 8)
    - Pizza Hut, undated (Box 8)
    - P-various including: Pagels Jewelers, PoFolks, Ponderosa Motor Inn, undated (Box 8)
  - Q/R, 1991 Dec.-1993 Feb., 35 sheets
    - Quail Creek Homes, undated (Box 8)
    - Ramada Inn, undated (Box 8)
    - Rodeway Inn, undated (Box 8)
    - Q/R-various including: Ralph Wilson Youth Clubs, Ranchouse Restaurant, Rio Development Corporation, Riverside Restaurant, Rylander's Best Hamburgers, undated (Box 8)
  - Sa-Se, 27 sheets
    - S & C Gas and Diesel, undated (Box 8)
    - Schlotsky's, undated (Box 8)
    - Scott and White Clinic and Hospital, undated (Box 8)
    - Southland (7-11), undated (Box 8)
    - Sa-Se-various including: Sandy's Home Place, Santa Pal, Sawdust and Satin, Service League of Temple, undated (Box 8)
  - Sh-Sw, 1966 July, 34 sheets (Box 9)
    - Sheffield Funeral Home, undated (Box 9)
    - Shell Gasoline, undated (Box 9)
    - Stagecoach Inn, undated (Box 9)
    - SummerFun USA, undated (Box 9)
    - Sh-Sw-various including: Sidles Custom Auto Sun Shades, Silver Post Jewelry, Smorgasbord House, Stockton Real Estate, undated (Box 9)
  - T, 1964 Aug.-1982 Apr., 71 sheets
    - Taco Bell, Apr. 1982 (Box 9)
    - Temple Junior College, undated (Box 9)
    - Texana National Bank, undated (Box 9)
    - Tranum Auto Dealerships, undated (Box 9)
    - T-various including: Temple Civic Theater, Texas Restaurant Association, Topsey Exotic Ranch, Triple D Tack and Western, Troy Fun Fest and Antique Tractor Show [for Temple Tourism, see "W"], undated (Box 9)
  - U/V, 1980 Dec., 9 sheets
    - University of Mary-Hardin Baylor, undated (Box 9)
    - V & M Drugstore, 1980 Dec. (Box 9)
    - U/V-various including: United Methodist Church, University of Central Texas, Varsity Motel, undated (Box 9)
  - W, 1982 Jan.-1991 Dec., 24 sheets
    - Wendlands Cattle and Horse Feeds, undated (Box 9)
    - Whataburger, undated (Box 9)
    - W-various including: Temple Tourism, W.C. Frank, Westfest, Williams Drug Stores, undated (Box 9)
  - X/Y/Z, 4 sheets
    - Young Pontiac, undated (Box 9)
    - Yowell's Boat Yard, undated (Box 9)
    - Zenith Laundry Cleaners, undated (Box 9)
    - Zrubec, Al, political ad, undated (Box 9)
- Slides Series, 1982-1988 and undated
  Comprises 25 slide sheets arranged alphabetically by the primary topic of each. Items that are included on a sheet but do not seem to fit the subject matter have been noted in the sheet listing.
  - Automobiles (and Taco Bell) 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Budweiser (and Busch) 1984-1985 and undated (Box 10)
  - Coke, 1982-1985 and undated (Box 10)
  - Construction, 1985 Sept., 2 sheets (Box 10)
  - Construction, 1985 Sept. 10, 2 sheets (Box 10)
  - Construction--Pole--Wide Angle, 1985 May 10, 2 sheets (Box 10)
  - Construction--Wide Angle, 1985 June, 2 sheets (Box 10)
  - Good Slides, 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Greasepaint, Chevy Camaro, Canyon Creek, Marlboro 1980s (Box 10)
  - L. Lynne Looney's Boards, 1984-1985 and undated (Box 10)
  - Marlboro, 1984-1985, 2 sheets (Box 10)
  - Marlboro [et al.] (includes miscellaneous ads), 1984-1985 and undated, 2 sheets (Box 10)
  - Marlboro [et al.] (includes miscellaneous ads), 1988 Nov. (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous, 1982-1986, 3 sheets (Box 10)
  - Posters (Carpets, 7-11, Hostages, KCEN-TV, etc.) 1982-1985 (Box 10)
  - Southwest Conference and Good Slides, 1983-1984 (Box 10)
- Negatives Series, 1978-1985 and undated
  Organized by type of negative--loose strips and a notebook. The negative strips were grouped by the Duplex Company and the original order has been maintained. The original order of the notebook was retained in processing. Arranged alphabetically by product type and client name, with the sleeve or page number of the image or images indicated afterward.
  - Loose negatives (billboards and location shots) (Box 11)
    - Adoption, undated, sleeve #8 (Box 11)
    - Adult Education, undated, sleeve # 8 (Box 11)
    - Billboard construction, sleeves #1, 7 (Box 11)
    - Coca Cola, undated, sleeve #9 (Box 11)
    - Damaged billboard, undated, sleeve #2 (Box 11)
    - Days Inn, undated, sleeve #6 (Box 11)
    - First National Bank, sleeve # 6 (Box 11)
    - Giovanni's Restaurant, sleeve # 9 (Box 11)
    - HBO, undated, sleeve #8 (Box 11)
    - Industrial sets, undated, sleeve #9 (Box 11)
    - K-Bob's Steakhouse, sleeve #6 (Box 11)
    - King's Daughters Clinic, undated, sleeve # 5 (Box 11)
    - Longhorn Caverns, undated, sleeve # 8 (Box 11)
    - Miller Beer, undated, sleeve # 7 (Box 11)
    - Outdoor Adventures, undated, sleeve # 9 (Box 11)
    - Partner Dance Club, undated, sleeve # 8 (Box 11)
    - Scenes from highway, undated, sleeves #3, 4 (Box 11)
    - Temple Bank, undated, sleeve # 8 (Box 11)
    - Texaco, undated, sleeve #8 (Box 11)
    - Texas Junior College, undated, sleeve # 8 (Box 11)
    - Twisted billboard for temp agency?, undated, sleeve # 6 (Box 11)
    - Viceroy cigarettes, undated, sleeve # 6 (Box 11)
  - Loose negatives (Duplex Advertising)
    - Air Force Reserve
      - 1970s, sleeve # 49 (Box 11)
      - 1978 July 14, sleeve # 12 (Box 11)
    - Alcoholic beverages, undated, sleeve #16 (Box 11)
    - Anchor Club, undated, sleeve # 20 (Box 11)
    - Andel Interiors, undated, sleeve # 17 (Box 11)
    - Apollo Solar Screens, 1980 Aug. 7, sleeve # 43 (Box 11)
    - Apparel, undated, sleeves #13, 18, 21-23 (Box 11)
    - Appliances, undated, sleeve #25 (Box 11)
    - Art gallery, undated, sleeve #18 (Box 11)
    - Arts and entertainment, undated, sleeve # 36 (Box 11)
    - Automobile dealers, undated, sleeves #15, 16, 18, 37 (Box 11)
    - Automobiles, undated, sleeves #21, 24, 25, 27, 29 (Box 11)
    - Automotive services, undated, sleeve #22 (Box 11)
    - Back to the Farm Restaurant, 1978 Sept. 21, sleeve # 10 (Box 11)
    - Banks
      - 1978 Dec. 13, sleeve # 13 (Box 11)
      - Undated, sleeves #14-16, 21, 22, 24-35, 38 a-b (Box 11)
    - Beechnut Chewing Tobacco, undated, sleeve #57 (Box 11)
    - Beef Jerky, undated, sleeve #18 (Box 11)
    - Bell County Expo Center, undated, sleeve # 18 (Box 11)
    - Belton real estate, undated, sleeve #56 (Box 11)
    - Best Western, undated, sleeve # 56 (Box 11)
    - Better Homes, 1978 July 14, sleeve # 12 (Box 11)
    - Beverages, undated, sleeves #15, 27, 28, 34, 35 (Box 11)
    - Blue Bell, 1980 Aug. 22, sleeve # 48a (Box 11)
    - Blue Bell ice cream, 1978 June 28, sleeve # 11 (Box 11)
    - Bonanza, 1980 Nov. 14, sleeve # 44 (Box 11)
    - Bud's Western Store, 1980 Aug. 7, sleeve # 43 (Box 11)
    - Builders, undated, sleeve #25 (Box 11)
    - Building supplies, undated, sleeve #25 (Box 11)
    - Burger King, undated, sleeve # 52 (Box 11)
    - Butter Krust bread, 1979 Mar. 26, sleeve # 50 (Box 11)
    - C. Bud Stockton Real Estate, 1979 Mar. 23, sleeve # 51 (Box 11)
    - Cable television, undated, sleeve #32 (Box 11)
    - Cablevision, 1978 June 21, sleeve # 10 (Box 11)
    - Candle Factory, 1978 June 28, sleeve # 11 (Box 11)
    - Capri, undated, sleeve #52 (Box 11)
    - Car and Truck Wash, 1980 Aug. 22, sleeve # 48a (Box 11)
    - Centennial Savings, 1980 Aug. 7, sleeve # 43 (Box 11)
    - Cigarettes, undated, sleeves #15, 31 (Box 11)
    - Circle K Food Stores, 1978 June 28, sleeve # 11 (Box 11)
    - Cleaning service, undated, sleeve #34 (Box 11)
    - Coca Cola, undated, sleeve # 17 (Box 11)
    - Coors
      - 1980 Aug. 7, sleeve # 43 (Box 11)
      - 1980 Aug. 22, sleeve # 48b (Box 11)
      - 1980 Nov. 14, sleeve # 44 (Box 11)
    - Corral Liquor Store, undated, sleeve # 18 (Box 11)
    - Corral Package Store, undated, sleeve # 20 (Box 11)
    - Creative Upholstery and Drapery, undated, sleeve #17 (Box 11)
    - Crim Furniture, 1978 Sept. 21, sleeve # 10 (Box 11)
    - Diamond Shamrock, undated, sleeve # 54 (Box 11)
    - Doc's Stop, undated, sleeve # 52 (Box 11)
    - Dodge, undated, sleeve #52 (Box 11)
    - Don Pedro's Mexican Restaurant
      - 1980 Aug. 21, sleeve # 43 (Box 11)
      - Undated, sleeve #17 (Box 11)
    - Dorer Jewelers
      - 1978 June 28, sleeve # 11 (Box 11)
      - Undated, sleeves #18, 19 (Box 11)
    - Education, undated, sleeve #35 (Box 11)
    - Elaine's Apparel, 1978 Sept. 21, sleeve # 10 (Box 11)
    - Entertainment, undated, sleeves #27-29, 32, 34, 35 (Box 11)
    - Exxon, undated, sleeve #20 (Box 11)
    - Falling down billboards, undated, sleeve # 42 (Box 11)
    - Family Waterpark, undated, sleeve # 56 (Box 11)
    - Farmers State Bank, undated, sleeve # 18 (Box 11)
    - Fina, undated, sleeve #54 (Box 11)
    - First National Bank
      - 1980 Mar. 22, sleeves # 48a-b (Box 11)
      - Undated, sleeve #19 (Box 11)
    - First National Kileen Bank, 1979 Mar. 26, sleeve # 50 (Box 11)
    - First National Motor Bank, 1979 Mar. 23, sleeve # 51 (Box 11)
    - First Southwest Realtors, 1978 June 28, sleeve # 11 (Box 11)
    - Food, undated, sleeves #24-28, 31 (Box 11)
    - Ford Tractors, 1980 Aug. 7, sleeve # 43 (Box 11)
    - Fort Hood National Bank, 1979 Mar. 26, sleeve # 50 (Box 11)
    - Frank's Anchor Club, sleeve # 17 (Box 11)
    - Frank's Lakeview, undated, sleeve # 20 (Box 11)
    - Frank's Lakeview Inn and Anchor Club, 1979 Mar. 26, sleeve # 50 (Box 11)
    - Fredericksburg National Bank, 1978 June 28, sleeve # 11 (Box 11)
    - Funeral homes, undated, sleeve #28-30, 33 (Box 11)
    - Gasoline, undated, sleeves #21, 22, 53 (Box 11)
    - Georgetown Hospital, undated, sleeve # 56 (Box 11)
    - Georgetown Style, undated, sleeves #19, 56 (Box 11)
    - Glamour Top Countertops, 1980 Aug. 7, sleeve # 43 (Box 11)
    - Golden Fried Chicken, undated, sleeve # 54 (Box 11)
    - Grandy's, 1980 Aug. 22, sleeve # 48b (Box 11)
    - Grocery stores
      - 1978 Dec. 13, sleeve # 13 (Box 11)
      - Undated, sleeve #31 (Box 11)
    - Gyms, undated, sleeve #26 (Box 11)